const questionList = {
    questions: [
    { // #1
        question:"What is the extension for a javascript file?",
        answers:[".js",".json",".html",".css"]
    },
    { // #2
        question:"What is the first index in an array?",
        answers:["0","1","a","first"]
    },
    { // #3
        question: "What is the output of the window.prompt() method?", 
        answers: ["string","number","boolean","There is no output"]
    },
    { // #4
        question: "What is the output of the window.confirm() method?",
        answers: ["boolean","string","number","There is no output"]
    },
    { // #5
        question: "What is the output of the window.alert() method?",
        answers: ["There is no output","string","number","boolean"]
    },
    { // #6
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a javascript datatype?",
        answers: ["letter","string","number","object"]
    },
    { // #7
        question: "Which method should be used to add a value to the end of an array?",
        answers: [".push()",".pop()",".shift()",".unshift()"]
    },
    { // #8
        question: "Which method should be used to remove a value from the beginning of an array?",
        answers: [".unshift()",".shift()",".push()",".pop()"]
    },
    { // #9
        question: "console.log(typeof '0'); will log what value?",
        answers: ["string","number","NaN","No value will be logged"]
    },
    { // #10
        question: "console.log(typeof true) will log what value?",
        answers: ["No value will be logged","string","number","boolean"]
    },
    { // #11
        question: "What code structure is used to iterate through lines of code mulitple times?",
        answers: ["loop","repeat","cycle","iterator"]
    },
    { // #12
        question: "What symbol is used to create an object variable?",
        answers: ["{}","[]","()","<>"]
    },
    { // #13
        question: "What symbol is used to create an array variable?",
        answers: ["[]","{}","()","<>"]
    },
    { // #14
        question: "What keyword is used to get the a variable's datatype?",
        answers: ["typeof","datatype","value","content"]
    },
    { // #15
        question: "Name this symbol: !",
        answers: ["bang operator","exclamation point","opposite","important"]
    },
    { // #16
        question: "In an object, each property assignment ends with what symbol?",
        answers: [";",",",":",")"]
    },
    { // #17
        question: "What is the HTML element used to connect a javascript file",
        answers: ["<script>","<link>","<source>","<javascript>"]
    },
    { // #18
        question: "What is the operator to assign a variable it's value?",
        answers: ["=","===","==",":"]
    },
    { // #19
        question: "What is the operator used to compare the value and type of two variables?",
        answers: ["===","==","=",":"]
    },
    { // #20
        question: "What is the operator used to compare only the value of two variables?",
        answers: ["==","=","===",":"]
    },
    { // #21
        question: "What kind of error occurs when a loop cannot escape itself?",
        answers: ["runtime","syntax","logic","compiling"]
    },
    { // #22
        question: "What is the keyword used to refer to the entirety of a webpage?",
        answers: ["window","page","webpage","screen"]
    },
    { // #23
        question: "What is the structure used for selection?",
        answers: ["if statement","for loop","while loop","sequencing"]
    },
    { // #24
        question: "var num = parseInt('four'); \n What value does the variable hold?",
        answers: ["NaN","four","4","undefined"]
    },
    { // #25
        question: "var num = 'four'; \n What value does the variable hold?",
        answers: ["four","4","NaN","undefined"]
    }
    ]
}